Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- Entrepreneurship & Personal Enterprise Program, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Exec Staff Assistant Search, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Faculty Development - Brian Chabot, 1996-1998 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Faculty Development and Mentorin Peter Hurst, 1995-1997 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Master Plan for Programs & Facilities, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Master Plan for Programs & Facilities- Meeting of the Buildings & Properties Committee of the Board Of Trustees, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Master Plan for Programs & Facilities, 1987-1988 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Metropolitan Development Association, 1995-1997 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Meyburg, Arnim, 1974-1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Miller, Frank W., 1986-1991 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Miller, Jay, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Mitre Corporation, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Morgan, James, 1994-1997 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- MSE, 1989-February 1990 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- MSE, February 1990-May 1991 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- MSE, June 1991-December 1991 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- MSE, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- MSE, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- MSE, 1993-1995 (Box 60, Folder 15-21)
- Neafsey, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- National Medal of Technology - Kenneth Iverson, CEO Nucor Corp., 1989 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Nelson, Frederick, 1990-1992 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- New Paltz, SUNY College at, 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 25-26)
- Newman, Floyd, R., 1971-1992 (Box 60, Folder 27-28)
- Nichols, Carol, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1977-1989 (Box 60, Folder 30-32)
- Annual Report - Agricultural & Biological Engineering, August 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Annual Report - Applied and Engineering Physics, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Annual Report - Chemical Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Annual Report - Civil & Environmental Engineering:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Annual Report - Communications Program:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Annual Report -Computer Science:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Annual Report Booklet-Computer Science:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Annual Report - National Nanofabrication Facility, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Annual Report -Electrical Engineering:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- [1: Faculty, 2: Honors: Faculty & Students, 3:Gifts & Capital Equipment, 4: Undergrad Education, Advising, & Minority Retention, 5: Enrollment Data] (Box 61)
- Annual Report -Electrical Engineering:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- [6: Student Course Surveys, 7: Degrees Awarded, 8: Research Contracts & Expenditures, 9: Colloquia Speakers] (Box 61)
- Annual Report -Electrical Engineering:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- [10: Faculty Research / Academic Contributions, 11: Faculty Profiles, 12: Appendices] (Box 61)
- Annual Report - Geological Sciences:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Annual Report - INSTOC:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Annual Report - Materials Science & Engineering:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Annual Report - Sibley School of Mechanical & Aerospace Engineering:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Annual Report - Laboratory of Plasma Studies:, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Annual Report - Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Annual Report - Theoretical & Applied Mechanics:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Annual Report- Administration, Planning & Facilities:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Annual Report- Engineering Advising Office:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Annual Report- Engineering Admissions:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Annual Report- Engineering Minority Programs Office:, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Annual Report - Engineering Placement & Career Services Office:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Annual Report - Engineering Professional Programs:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Annual Report - Engineering Public Affairs Office, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Annual Report - Engineering Registrar's Office:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Annual Report - Engineering Women's Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Annual Report - Heads of Faculty Committees:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Annual Report - Affirmative Action Committee:, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Affirmative Action Data, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Annual Report, Women's Programs in Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Annual Report, Theoretical & Applied Mechanics, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Annual Report, Undergraduate Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Annual Report, Heads of Faculty Committees, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 34)
- Annual Report, Engineering Admissions, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 35)
- Annual Report, Engineering Advising, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 36)
- Annual Report, Agricultural & Biological Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 37)
- [Contents, ABEN Annual Report] (Box 61)
- Annual Report, Agricultural & Biological Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 38)
- [Human Resources & Programs, Undergrad Programs] (Box 61)
- Annual Report, Applied & Engineering Physics, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 39)
- Annual Report, Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 40)
- Annual Report, Engineering Communications Program, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 41)
- Annual Report, Computer Science, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 42)
- Annual Report, Engineering Cooperative Program, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 43)
- Annual Report, Engineering Corporate Relations Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 44)
- Annual Report, Electrical Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 45)
- Annual Report, Electronic Packaging, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 46)
- Annual Report, Geological Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 47)
- Annual Report, Materials Science & Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 48)
- Annual Report, INSTOC, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 49)
- Annual Report, Master of Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 50)
- Annual Report, Mechanical & Aerospace Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 51)
- Engineering Minority Programs Office: Goals And Directions for Academic Year, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 52)
- Annual Report, Nuclear Science and Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 53)
- Annual Report, Operations Research And Industrial Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 54)
- Annual Report, Engineering Placement, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 55)
- Office (Box 61)
- Annual Report, Laboratory of Plasma Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 56)
- Annual Report, Public Affairs Office, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 57)
- Annual Report, Engineering Publications, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 58)
- Annual Report, Engineering Registrar's Office, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 59)
- Annual Report Year 3- Synthesis: A National Engineering Education Coalition, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 60)
- Annual Report Year 3-Appendices: Synthesis: A National Engineering Education Coalition, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 61)
- College of Engineering - Public Affairs - Annual Reports and Goals, 1980-1983 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- College of Engineering - Public Affairs - Annual Reports and Goals, 1983-1985 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- College of Engineering - Public Affairs - Annual Reports and Goals, 1985-1987 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Strategic Plan, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions- vol. 2 Faculty Committee - A&EP, 1991-1992 (Box 62, Folder book 1)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 4 LPS - Electronic Packaging Program, 1991-1992 (Box 62, Folder book 2)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 1, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder book 3)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder book 4)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder book 5)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 1 Dean's Annual Report - A&EP, 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder book 6)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 2, CEE - ORIE, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder book 1)
- Master of Engineering (CIVIL) Engineering Management Project 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder book 2)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 2, CEE - T&AM, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder book 3)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 3, Electronic Packaging Program-Research Units, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder book 4)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 1, Deans Annual Report - A&EP, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder book 5)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 3, CEE - GS, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder book 6)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 1, Deans Annual Report - Undergrad Program, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder book 7)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering and Divisions - vol. 3, T&AM Research Units, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder book 8)
- Executive Summary - Center for Theory & Simulation in Science & Engineering - EE, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Explorations in Engineering Final Report, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- The Master Plan for Engineering Facilities at Cornell University, Progress Report, Summer 1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- The Master Plan for Engineering Facilities at Cornell University, Summary Report, Summer 1986 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Engineering Library, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Engineering Library, 1986-1989 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Engineering Library, 1990-1992 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Engineering Library, 1993-1998 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- ERIF Proposal - letter to the President of the University, August 1996 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- ERIF Proposal, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Engineering Research & Instructional Facility (ERIF), 1994-October 1995 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- ERIF, November 1995-June 1996 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- ERIF, July-August 1996 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- ERIF and other information, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- ERIF documents, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- SRC Annual Report of Research, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Representative Recent Publications of MSE, 1989-1994 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Annual Report Public Affairs Office, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- SRC Annual Report of Research, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Duffield Hall, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Duffield Hall, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- ASTI, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- ERIF, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- ERIF, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- SiGe Nanoelectronics & Advanced Processes, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Annual Reports College of Engineering-, 1988-1989 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Annual Report: Department of Theoretical and Applied Mechanics, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Annual Report: School of Operations Research and Industrial Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Annual Report: Laboratory of Plasma Studies, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Annual Report to the Dean of Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Annual Report: Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Annual Report: Undergraduate Programs & Student Services, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- ABEN Department: Program Report Summary, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Annual Report: School of Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Contract Review Poster Session, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Annual Report: Center for Applied Mathematics, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Annual Report: School of Applied Engineering and Physics, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Annual Report: School of Chemical Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Annual Report: Department of Geological Sciences, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Annual Report: School of Electrical Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Annual Report; Department of Computer Science, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Annual Highlights: Engineering Communications Program, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Annual Report: School of Applied and Engineering Physics, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Annual Report: School of Chemical Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Annual Report: School of Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Annual Report: Department of Computer Science, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Annual Report: School of Electrical Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Annual Report: School of Electrical Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Annual Report: Department of Geological Sciences & INSTOC, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Annual Report: Department of Materials Science and Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Annual Report: Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Annual Report: School of Operations Research and Industrial Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Annual Report: Laboratory of Plasma Studies August, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Annual Report: Theoretical and Applied Mechanics, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Annual Report: Office of Administration, Planning and Facilities, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- Annual Report: Undergraduate Programs and Student Services, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- Annual Report: Affirmative Action Committee Report, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Annual Report: Bioengineering, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 32)
- Annual Report: Engineering College's Grievance Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Annual Report: Admissions Advisory Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Annual Report: Engineering Policy Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 35)
- Annual Report: Nominating Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 36)
- Annual Report: CCGB, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 37)
- Annual Report: Undergraduate Programs & Student Services, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 38)
- Annual Report: Undergraduate Programs & Student Services, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 39-40)
- Annual Report: Undergraduate Programs & Student Services, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 41-43)
- Annual Report: College of Engineering, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 44-49)
- Awards, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Best Practices, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Blakely (Atomic Steps on Si), 1996 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Budget Envelope Discussion, 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Budget Reduction, 1996-1995 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Centers & Institutes, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Climate Assessment, April 1998 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Climate Assessment, Part 2, April 1998 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Climate Faculty Meetings, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- College Rankings, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Committee for the Future of Higher Education, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Corporate Relations, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Culture, 1996-1998 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Culture - Human Resource Material, 1993-1998 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Duffield - Design Concepts for Schematic Site Plans, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Duffield - Project Management, 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Endowed Chairs, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 17-19)
- Engineering College Budget & Size Discussions, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Engineering 150 - Freshmen Advising (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Genomics, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- McGuire, Stephen, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Faculty Promotions, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Applied and Engineering Physics, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Chemical Engineering, 1999-2000 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Computer Science, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Electrical Engineering, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Geological Sciences, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- Material Science and Engineering, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1992-1998 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- Nuclear Science and Engineering, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- Theoretical and Applied Mechanics, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- Appointments, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 36)
- Associate Dean, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 37)
- Waste Management Institute, 1987-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Web Genesis / The Globe, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Web Communications (University), December 1998 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Webster Research Center, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Weiss Presidential Fellows, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Weiss Presidential Fellows, 1996-1998 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Wells College Agreement, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Status of Women Committees, 1991-1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Status of Women Committees, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Women in Engineering, 1986-1989 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Women in Engineering, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Women in Engineering, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Women in Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Women in Engineering, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Women in Engineering, 1994-1998 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Women & Minorities Grant (NSF), 1991 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1972-1980 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1981-1989 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1993-1995 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1996-1999 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- Summary Report: School of Electrical Engineering, 1986 (Box 67, Folder book 1)
- Undergraduate Research Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder book 2)
- Undergraduate Research Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 67, Folder book 3)
- Cornell University College of Engineering Master Plan Technical Report, 1986 (Box 67, Folder book 4)
- Contains an Electronic Gavel Bell (Box 68, Folder NA)
- Engineers Magazine, January and April 1997 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Greenberg, Donald:, 1984-1991 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Greenberg, Donald:, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Gubbins, Keith, 1976-1987 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Gubbins, Keith, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Commendation and Appreciation Letter from the Engineering College Council to President Dale R. Corson, May 8, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Cornell Annotation Issues 4 - 16 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Cornell Annotation Issues 17 - 32 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Cornell Annotation Issues 33 - 42 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Cornell Annotation Issues 42 - 52 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Proposal to NSF for a Science and Technology Center for Computer Graphics and Scientific Visualization -, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Computing and Information Science at Cornell - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Studies in Theoretical Biology: A Collection of Undergraduate Research -Cornell-SACNAS Summer Program, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Agricultural and Biological Engineering - Academic Review, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- College of Engineering Yearbook - Sundial -, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Oversized Items (Box 69, Folder NA)
- Engineering College Council & Cornell Society of Engineers Resolutions (Box 69, Folder NA)
- Commencement, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Commencement, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Commencement, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- University Computing Board, July 1982-September 1989 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- University Engineering Conference, April 19990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Continuing Education, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Continuing Education, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Continuing Education, January-June 1989 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Continuing Education, July-October 1989 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Continuing Education, November-December 1989 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Continuing Education, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Cornell Engineer (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Ezra C. Cornell Professorship Program -, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- John Corning - IBM Visiting Fellow -, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Cornell Society of Engineers, July 1, 1984-June 30, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Cornell Society of Engineers, July 1, 1985-June 30, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Cornell Research Council until 1984 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Cornell Research Council, 1984-1987 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Cornell Research Foundation, 1984-1987 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Craig, AP -, 1987-1990 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Cranch, Edmund -, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Davis, Harriet Graduate Fellowship -, 1984-1990 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Deans - Big Ten Meetings -, 1983-1988 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Deitrick, Carroll Trust, December 7, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Eastman, Lester, 1977-1988 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- EDUCOM, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Egner, Joan, Vice Provost, 1982-1987 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Electrical Engineering Acting Director Search, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, Power Systems Advisory, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Elsas, Norman -, 1983-1990 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, September 25-26 1992 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- ECC Meeting, April 1992 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- ECC Meeting, September 1991 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- ECC Meeting, April 1991 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- ECC Meeting, September 1990 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- ECC Meeting, April 1990 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- ECC Meeting, April 1989 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- ECC Meeting, October 1989 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- ECC Meeting, October 21-22, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Engineering College Council- General, July 1988-October 1989 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Engineering College Council- General, July 1986-June 30, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Entrepreneur of the year Program, July 1986-March 1990 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Engineering Women's Club Directory (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Facilities - ad hoc Planning Group for Eng. Faculty, May 1985-September 1986 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- Faculty, Engineering - Administrative Changes, 1971-1989 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- Hogin, Phil -, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- Long, Jorie -, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- Margiloff, I.B., 1969-1986 (Box 71, Folder 27)
- Master of Engineering (GPPC), October-December 1991 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Master of Engineering (GPPC), January-September 1991 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Master of Engineering (GPPC), 1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Master of Engineering (GPPC), 1989 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Mathematics, 1972-1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- McCarthy, Rolin H. (re: Geol. Sc. Bldg) (Box 72, Folder 6)
- McMullen Scholarships, 1971-1984 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Mechanical & Aerospace Engineering, 1989-90 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- "O" (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Promotion & Tenure Guidelines & Revisions, 1980-1984 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- RESEARCH - A Comprehensive Sponsored Research System (Box 72, Folder 11)
- "W", 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Wang Institute for Graduate Studies (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Western Electric Co. (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Worcester Polytechnic Institute (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Word Processing Report (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Deaths, 1988-1989 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Deaths, 1982-1987 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Deaths, 1980-1982 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Deaths, 1973-1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Degrees, Authorized (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Degree Designation (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Degree Program Comments, May 1965 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Degree Program (New)Modification, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- Denver, University of, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Associate Dean Design (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Design Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 72, Folder 27)
- Design - NASA (Box 72, Folder 28)
- Design Search Committee, January 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Design Publication, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Design - Engineering Doctorate Level, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Design Study, 1964-1969 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Development - Corporate Giving, 1968-1972 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Development Committee, College A. Schultz Jr., Chairman, 19778-1980 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- University Development "The Cornell Campaign", 1979-1981 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Development Trips A. Schultz, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Development Berth, D.F., 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Development Berth, D.F., 1973-1981 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Development Trips T.E. Everhart, 1979-1983 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Dickason, D.G., 1966-1979 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Dill, John (Computer Graphics), 1980-1984 (Box 73, Folder 13)